I am liking ICICI Lombard for earning 10%.
Here we have seen
that as per the calculations, after a big rally earlier, there was
a correction in the stock
from 2250 to
2050-2080. From there, the stock has again
created a good momentum in the last three days and is regaining its strength. At the same time, the
stock has again come above its 20-day
external moving average
and is standing strong. If
we look at the weekly chart, it is completely an up
trending chart after June 2024 and just
this last week there was a retest of
important moving averages. I
feel that ICICI Lombard should be taken at
lower levels or current price or on a small
dip. Stop loss of 2140
and target of 2220 to 2250,
I see it coming here. If it sustains above 2250 then
A new upside
can open here, so buy it for short term, but if the
stock goes above 2250, then do
not rush to sell it and keep training it, it is
absolutely right for the upwards,
so this is the suggestion for you to buy ICICI Lombard at an earning of Rs 10,
Sar ji.